(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
HAPPY!
It's time to PARTY!
Are you ready?
FUWA MOCO!
BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU
白上フブキ
Shirakami Fubuki
大神ミオ
Ookami Mio
宝鐘マリン
Houshou Marine
尾丸ポルカ
Omaru Polka
博衣こより
Hakui Koyori
シオリ・ノヴェラ
Shiori Novella
古石ビジュゥ
Koseki Bijou
ネリッサ・レイヴンクロフト
Nerissa Ravenercross
HERE WE GO!
Hold me baby 踊ろうよ Sunday
Hold me baby, let's dance, it's Sunday
Touch me baby 気分は Holiday
Touch me baby, I feel like it's a holiday
PARTY@NIGHT
Have a PARTY NIGHT!
嫌なこと全部　忘れちゃおう
Let's forget all the bad things
一晩眠って　目覚めたらハッピーが
Sleep through the night, and wake up to happiness
夢の途中で　出会う不思議
A mystery encountered in the middle of a dream
悪夢を食べてる　獏たちもグッドフレンド
Even the tapirs who eat nightmares are good friends
いつもならば　お喋りもしない
Usually, we wouldn't even talk
窮屈なヒト　陽気なリズムで変身
Stuffy people transform with a cheerful rhythm
Hold me baby　ノリノリParty
Hold me baby, a grooving Party
瞳まで　輝いて
Even your eyes are sparkling
Touch me baby　are you ready OK?
Touch me baby, are you ready OK?
楽しもう　君も
Let's have fun, you too
Hold me baby　踊ろうよSunday
Hold me baby, let's dance, Sunday
ステップを　踏みましょう
Let's keep the step
Touch me baby　気分はHoliday
Touch me baby, feeling like a Holiday
スペシャルな　時を
A special time
ハイ！ ハイ！
Hai! Hai!
疲れすぎて　臆病な日には
On days when you're too tired and timid
まぶた閉じて　アクセスしてみて
Close your eyes and try to access it
Have a PARTY NIGHT!
Hold me baby　ウキウキLady
Hold me baby, cheerful Lady
ストレスは　溜めないで
Don't let stress build up
Touch me baby　キラキラBody
Touch me baby, sparkling Body
リフレッシュ　しよう
Let's refresh ourselves
Hold me baby　踊ろよSunday
Hold me baby, let's dance, Sunday
心にも　栄養を
Nourishment for the heart too
Touch me baby　気分はHoliday
Touch me baby, feeling like a Holiday
星空の　メロディ
A melody of the starry sky
Hold me baby　ウキウキLady
Hold me baby, cheerful Lady
All together with us! ハイ！ ハイ！
All together with us! Hai! Hai!
Touch me baby　キラキラBody
Touch me baby, sparkling Body
ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
Hold me baby　ウキウキLady
Hold me baby, cheerful Lady
ふわふわ　もこもこ
Fuwafuwa Mokomoko
魔界の番犬シスターズ☆☆
Demon World guard dog sisters☆☆
この世界に爆誕 "BAU"DOLです
Born into this world, we are "BAU"DOLs
Here we go! Bau Bau!!
Fuwawa!!
Mococo!!
FUWA + MOKO wa FUWAMOKO
FUWA + MOKO is FUWAMOKO
FUWAMOCO!!
Bau Bau~!!
Wake up したら 君に Morning
When you wake up, Morning to you
New な出会い 嗅ぎきかせ Search して
New encounters, sniff them out and Search
DOGGY DOGGY 右に左
DOGGY DOGGY right and left
Bau Bau Bau
悩んでいても 来ちゃう Future
Even if you're worried, the Future will come
まずは目の前の道 Step して
First, take a Step on the path before you
Happy Lucky Puppy
一緒に歩こうよ
Let's walk together
ドーナツの穴の中には
Inside the donut hole
きっときっと
Surely, surely
夢が詰まってるから
Dreams are packed within
ふわふわ もこもこ 魔界の番犬シスターズ☆☆
Fuwafuwa Mokomoko, Demon World guard dog sisters☆☆
2匹が揃えば もう 大騒ぎ
When the two are together, it's a huge commotion
もあもあ ハロハロ 迷わずに Go my way
Mmore mmore, hello hello, Go my way without hesitation
君の絶対味方 "BAU"DOLです
We're your absolute allies, "BAU"DOLs
Bau Bau!!
Fuwawa!!
Mococo!!
FUWA + MOKO wa FUWAMOKO
FUWA + MOKO is FUWAMOKO
FUWAMOCO!!!
Bau Bau~!!
ひとりじゃないよ We're together
You're not alone, We're together
Heart 繋がってる 君と Chat して
Hearts connected, Chatting with you
Fluffy Puffy Yappy
一緒に歌おうよ
Let's sing together
ドーナツの穴の向こうへ
Beyond the donut hole
きっときっと
Surely, surely
君が待っているから
Because you are waiting there
ふわふわ もこもこ 魔界の番犬シスターズ☆☆
Fuwafuwa Mokomoko, Demon World guard dog sisters☆☆
2匹が揃えば もう 止まらない
When the two are together, they won't stop
お耳も Ear!!
Ears too, Ear!!
尻尾も BunBun!!
Tails too, BunBun!!
おさわりは厳禁XX
Touching is strictly forbiddenXX
スリル満点爆弾 "BAU"DOLです
A thrill-filled bomb, we are "BAU"DOLs
Bau Bau!!
Hey!! Ruffians!!
It's our birthday, huh?
Can I get a heck yeah!?
Let's shout "BAU"!!
Bau!! Bau!! Bau!! Bau!!...
Now, hear the howling of my soul!!
BAU!!
Are you ready?!
モコちゃん！！ 生誕だから可愛く歌おうねって言ったでしょ！
Mococo-chan!! I told you we were going to sing cutely since it's our birthday!
bau bau...
じゃあBメロから･･･せーの！
Well then, from the B-melody... ready, set!
ドーナツリングに誓って ずっと ずっと
I swear on the donut ring, that always, always...
笑顔を守るから ふわふわ Wa! Foo!!
I'll protect your smile. Fuwa fuwa! Wa! Foo!!
もこもこ！ 魔界の番犬シスターズ
Moko moko! The underworld guard dog sisters
2匹が揃えば もう大騒ぎ
When the two of us are together, it's a huge commotion
もあもあ ハロハロ 迷わずに Go my way
Moo moo! Hello hello! Without hesitation, Go my way
君の絶対味方 “BAU”DOLです
We are your absolute allies, BAU-DOLs
この世界に爆誕 “BAU”DOLです
Born into this world, BAU-DOLs
Fuwawa!! Mococo!! FUWA-MOKO! FUWAMOKO!
FUWAMOCO!! Born to be BAU!! BAU BAU~!!
BAU BAU!! Thank you for joining us tonight!
For a very special time, our FuwaMoco Birthday Party Night!
It's our first birthday live ever, right? Otanjoubi Omedetou!
Otanjoubi! Seitan-sai!
Happy Birthday! Birthday Festival!
Ah, but uh, just exactly whose birthday is it, huh?
Ah, ah, it's Mococo-chan's! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
I'm not a chihuahua, I'm Fuwawa! I'm Fuwawa!
I'm Fuwawa! I'm Mococo!
Together we're FuwaMoco! Bau Bau!!
And it's my birthday! It's my birthday!
It's our birthday! Bau Bau!!
Ah, if you're a little confused right now, that's okay
because our birthdays are technically apart.
Yeah! But mine is February 1st.
And mine is on the 2nd! Second, oh!
And that's why today's concert is right in between them!
Right in between! Yeah, uh! Makes sense, yeah, Bau Bau!
Well, you know, it's our first ever birthday live,
so we want to have an especially fun time together!
That's why the party night, party night! Oh, yeah!
The good part of the party is always the hashtag!
Hashtag, oh! So, please make sure to use our hashtag!
Hashtag #FWMCbday25 right up here! This way!
That's the hashtag! You see it? Don't get it wrong!
Hashtag! And please put your thoughts and screenshots there,
and after everything, we'll go take a look at them after the live!
Like, but, like, besides our hashtag, Mococo-chan...
Look! Look at our stage! Bau Bau! Bau Bau! Oh!
And you know, I think this stage might be a little bit sweet, cute!
Oh, sweet, oh, yeah!
Mococo-chan, keep your paws off of the donuts, okay?
Ah, not right now... not yet!
Well, Mococo-chan, you're going to take care of the clean up of the stage.
Staff-san will take care of it! Yeah, thank you!
You know, sweet... and I think we can also guarantee
that maybe things might be a little bit silly today too!
Silly, oh! Especially with all the fun we have planned!
Yeah, you know, and our special guests! Oh, special guests! Yeah!
So we hope that you'll cheer us on lots and lots
as we sing and dance together with them, okay? Oh, wow!
For our next song, we wanted to share a song that's very special to us.
It kind of goes back to our roots... oh, our roots!
Our demon roots! Grrr... Bau Bau! Yeah, oh!
Fuwamoco are very fluffy, fuzzy, and silly, but...
we're demon dogs, you know! Very hungry demon dogs! Oh, bau, yeah!
You know, we might look cute, but don't doubt our strength, okay?
Yeah! Oh! Got it! Oh!
Please listen to our next song then. Kaibutsu.
Please listen to our next song then. Monster.
怪物
Monster
素晴らしき世界に今日も乾杯
Cheers to this wonderful world again today
街に飛び交う笑い声も
Even the laughter echoing through the city
見て見ぬふりしてるだけの作りもんさ
is just a fabrication we pretend not to see
気が触れそうだ
I feel like I'm going crazy
クラクラするほどの良い匂いが ツンと刺した鼻の奥
The scent, so sweet it makes me dizzy, pricks the back of my nose
目を醒ます本能のまま
Following my waking instincts
今日は誰の番だ？
whose turn is it today?
この世界で何ができるのか
What can I do in this world?
僕には何ができるのか
What can I do?
ただその真っ黒な目から
Just so that from those pitch-black eyes
涙こぼれ落ちないように
tears don't spill
Ah 願う未来に
Ah, to the future I wish for
何度でもずっと 喰らいつく
I'll keep biting into it over and over
この間違いだらけの世界の中
In this world full of mistakes
君には笑ってほしいから
I want you to be smiling
もう誰も傷つけない
I don't want to hurt anyone anymore
強く強くなりたいんだよ
I want to become strong, so strong
僕が僕でいられるように
So that I can remain myself
素晴らしき世界は今日も安泰
The wonderful world is peaceful again today
街に渦巻く悪い話も
Even the bad rumors swirling in the city
知らない知らないふりして目を逸らした
I pretended not to know and looked away
正気の沙汰じゃないな
This isn't sanity
真面目に着飾った行進
A march dressed in seriousness
鳴らす足音が弾む
the sound of footsteps bouncing
行き先は消えない消えない味が染み付いている
The destination is stained with an indelible, lingering taste
裏側の世界
The world on the other side
Ah...
清く正しく生きること
Living purely and honestly
誰も悲しませずに生きること
living without making anyone sad
はみ出さず真っ直ぐに生きること
Living straight without straying
それが間違わないで生きること？
is that what it means to live without mistakes?
ありのまま生きることが正義か
Is living as you are justice?
騙し騙し生きるのは正義か
Is living by deceiving justice?
僕の在るべき姿とは何だ
What is the way I should be?
本当の僕は誰何者なんだ
Who am I really?
教えてくれよ
Tell me!
今日も答えのない世界の中で
Even today, in a world without answers
願ってるんだよ
I'm wishing
不器用だけれど
Awkward as I am
いつまでも君とただ笑っていたいから
I just want to be laughing with you forever
跳ねる心臓が体揺らし
My racing heart shakes my body
叫ぶんだよ
and screams
今こそ動き出せ
Move out now!
Ah 弱い自分を
Ah, my weak self
何度でもずっと 喰らいつく
I'll keep biting into it over and over
この間違いだらけの世界の中
In this world full of mistakes
君には笑ってほしいから
I want you to be smiling
もう誰も泣かないよう
So that no one cries anymore
強く強くなりたいんだよ
I want to become strong, so strong
僕が僕でいられるように
So that I can remain myself
ただ君を守る
Just to protect you
そのために走る 走る 走るんだよ
for that, I'll run, run, run
僕の中の僕を超える
Exceeding the me within myself
悲しみキャリブレーション
Kanashimi Calibration
口づけさえ今は悲しいだけ
Even a kiss is only sad now
君の心
Your heart
どこか置き去りのまま
remains left behind somewhere
当たり前に見えたあの優しさ
That kindness that seemed so natural
きっと他の誰かの
will surely become
ものになる
someone else's
揺れる心
Trembling heart
迷う気持ち
lost feelings
どこにおけばいいの
where should I put them?
重なりあう手も
Our overlapping hands
古くさくないの
aren't old-fashioned
焦る私
I'm panicking
孤独になる
getting lonely
二人きりなのに
even though it's just the two of us
届かない
Can't reach
声も届かない
even my voice can't reach
何もできない私
I can't do anything
ただのマリオネット
just a marionette
君目指したディスティネーション
The destination aiming for you
最後の言葉 スローモーション
final words in slow motion
聞きたくない
I don't want to hear
知りたくもない
I don't want to know
チグハグになるコンビネーション
A combination that's becoming mismatched
泣き出しそうなグラデーション
A gradation that looks like it's about to cry
私 どんな顔でいればいいかな
What kind of face should I make?
冗談だよね
It's a joke, right?
好きだよって言ってよ
Tell me you love me
胸に刺さる 棘はいつからだよ
Since when was this thorn stuck in my heart?
見えない壁 それは気づかぬフリ
An invisible wall, I pretend not to notice it
優しいフリ 今更しなくても
You don't have to pretend to be kind now
行きと分かってるのにできないの
I know how it goes, but I just can't do it
望む愛は昔ほど 手に入らないもの
The love I want is no longer as easy to get
他の誰かでは埋められないもの
Something that no one else can fill
疑問さえも不満さえも出てるのに
Even though doubts and frustrations are surfacing
私動けない
I can't move
想い許せない
I can't forgive these feelings
後悔しちゃう 心 抑えきれない
I'll regret it, I can't hold back my heart
さよならの場所 インビテーション
An invitation to the place of goodbye
行きたくないよ テンプテーション
I don't want to go, temptation
傷ついても そばにいたいよ
Even if I get hurt, I want to be by your side
悲しい気持ち キャリブレーション
Sad feelings, calibration
受け入れないよ レボリューション
I won't accept it, revolution
強がることしか 今はできない
All I can do now is pretend to be strong
冗談だよね
It's a joke, right?
嘘だよって言ってよ
Tell me it's a lie
インスピレーション
Inspiration!
プロモーション
Promotion!
コンビネーション
Combination!
グラデーション
Gradation!
インビテーション
Invitation!
テンプテーション
Temptation!
レボリューション
Revolution!
悲しみキャリブレーション！
Kanashimi Calibration!
君が目指した ディスティネーション
The destination you aimed for
最後の言葉 スローモーション
The final words in slow motion
聞きたくない 知りたくもない
I don't want to hear it, I don't even want to know
チグハグになる コンビネーション
A combination that's becoming mismatched
泣き出しそうな グラデーション
A gradation that looks like it's about to cry
もう君に 甘えちゃいけないかな
Can I no longer depend on you?
大好きな人
My beloved person
さよなら さよなら
Goodbye, goodbye
Bau bau!
We surprised you, Ruffians!
And now Fuwawa and Mococo with Advent's Demon Dogs of the Throne, Bau Bau!
You get it now, Ruffians?
Bau Bau!
We hope you enjoyed seeing just a bit more of our power and not just cute fluff and fuzz all the time.
And you know, together with Advent, we were able to sing...
...an idol song that we love called Kanashimi Calibration.
And you know, this song has been really, really special to us...
...because it was a song that we wanted to sing together with Advent all the way back when we were together in the cell.
And Ruffians, your calls were absolutely amazing!
Great job, Ruffians! Thank you!
Destination! Right? Very, very hot!
Yeah, you gave us so much power during that last part of our performance there.
Thank you, Ruffians!
But, you know, we've shown you a little bite of what these Demon Dogs have.
But we want to be able to show the Ruffians lots of different sides of FuwaMoco today, right?
Right!
That side? All the sides.
But, you know, the next side is... it's a challenging side, Mocchan.
It's going to be a bit of a challenge, okay?
You know, FuwaMoco, we wanted to show a bit more of a "feeling" side.
A feeling side... Oh, maybe a bit more...
...sexy?
Sexy? Sexy?
Yeah, 'cause you know, Mococo is sexy, right?
Right?
Huh?
Huh? Do I hear your voice?
Yes!
No, no, no.
Yes! Well, I'll prove it to you, okay?
Okay, Mococo-sa, you do your best, okay?
Yeah!
Ugh, but to be able to do that, we've prepared some solo songs for you today!
Yay! Bau Bau!
No...
Not only is it going to be a bit of a challenge, but it'll be our first time dancing and singing on our own for you!
So, I... to tell the truth, I'm a little bit nervous.
Huh? Mococo-chan, nervous?
Oh no way! Never happened! Oh!
So, I'll do my best, but you need to make sure to give me lots of headpats, okay?
I'll give you headpats too!
Yeah!
Okay! Well, I'm too nervous right now.
Okay, Mococo-chan, let's decide who's going to go...
No!
Huh?
I'm... because this is now... I want to go first! I want it! Yeah.
Okay, well, Mococo-chan, you have to go after though, okay?
I guess.
Let- Let me do it otherwise!
Huh? Yeah!
Do your best, okay?
Okay!
Bye bye!
Bau Bau!
Well, Bau Bau!
I guess it's time for me to take you back a few years with this next song.
Please listen to: MUGO・ん…色っぽい.
MUGO・ん…色っぽい
Lyrics: 中島みゆき Music: 後藤次利
MUGO...n... Ippoi
Lyrics: Miyuki Nakajima Music: Tsugutoshi Goto
言えないのよ
I can't say it
言いたいことならどれくらい
How much is there that I want to say
あるかわからなくあふれてる
It's overflowing so much I don't even know
私こちらの
I am normally
お喋りだわ
quite a chatterbox
言いたいことならあなたには
There are things I want to say to you
あとからあとからあふれてる
overflowing one after another
私意外と
I am unexpectedly
お喋りだわ なのに
quite a chatterbox, and yet
いざとなるとうちきになる
when the time comes, I become shy
遠い場所から
From a far away place
何度も話しかけてるのに
even though I've spoken to you many times
目と目で通じ合う
Communicating eye to eye
かすかに、ん、色っぽい
faintly, hmm, looking sexy
目と目で通じ合う
Communicating eye to eye
そういう仲になりたいわ
that's the kind of relationship I want to have
無言 いくじなしね
Silence, how cowardly
無言 寂しがりね
Silence, how lonely
言いたいことならあの日から
The things I've wanted to say since that day
誰にも負けずにあふれてる
are overflowing more than anyone else's
私気持ちは
My feelings are
わがままだわ なのに
quite selfish, and yet
いざとなるとうちきになる
when the time comes, I become shy
書いた手紙も
Even the letter I wrote
しまい込んで誰もしらない
I've tucked it away and no one knows
目と目で通じ合う
Communicating eye to eye
かすかに、ん、色っぽい
faintly, hmm, looking sexy
目と目で通じ合う
Communicating eye to eye
そういう仲になりたいわ
that's the kind of relationship I want to have
目と目で通じ合う
Communicating eye to eye
かすかに、ん、色っぽい
faintly, hmm, looking sexy
目と目で通じ合う
Communicating eye to eye
そういう仲になりたいわ
that's the kind of relationship I want to have
明日 少し勇気を出して
Tomorrow, I'll have a little courage
視線投げてみようかしら
and maybe I'll try to catch your eye
目と目で通じ合う
Communicating eye to eye
かすかに、ん、色っぽい
faintly, hmm, looking sexy
目と目で通じ合う
Communicating eye to eye
そういう仲になりたいわ
that's the kind of relationship I want to have
無言 いくじなしね
Silence, how cowardly
無言 寂しがりね
Silence, how lonely
無言 いくじなしね
Silence, how cowardly
無言 寂しがりね
Silence, how lonely
言えないのよ
I can't say it
…さよなら。
...Goodbye.
筋肉を
Muscles...
筋肉を触らせてよ
Let me touch your muscles
どんな感じなのかい？
What do they feel like?
興味があるのよ
I'm curious
男の子って不思議だね
Boys are mysterious, aren't they?
わるきー
Warukii
Hey, you know, Mococo is sexy too, right?
Is it okay if I brush up against those big muscles of yours?
Bau bau!
今日のバッグなんだか重くて
My bag today is somehow heavy
そう 誰かに持たせて欲しかった
Yes, I wanted someone to carry it for me
だから ちょっと甘えてみて
So I tried acting a bit spoiled
ハートを釣ってみた
And tried to hook your heart
甘い溜息一つチラリと見て
Give a quick glance at one sweet sigh
おねだりするのよ わるきー
And start begging, the bad girl
筋肉を触らせてよ どれくらい硬いの？
Let me touch your muscles, how hard are they?
女の子には興味津々
Girls are very curious
逞しさ見てみたいのよ
I want to see your sturdiness
どんな感じなのかい？
What does it feel like?
ワクワクしてるわ
I'm getting excited
上腕二頭筋てセクシーだね
Biceps are sexy, aren't they?
これを持って！
Hold this!
男らしいマッチョがタイプよ
Manly macho guys are my type
でも 本当はそんなことないけど
But actually, that's not really true
じっと見つめおだててあげなきゃ
I have to stare at you and flatter you
何も釣れないわ
Or I won't catch anything
こっちが頼んじゃなくてやらせてくれて
It's not that I'm asking, but let me do it
頼まれるように わるきー
So that you ask me instead, the bad girl
筋肉に抱かれたいの いつの日がどこかで
I want to be embraced by muscles, someday, somewhere
私のために頑張って
Do your best for me
筋肉に抱かれたいの 折れるくらい強く
I want to be embraced by muscles, as strong as if they'd break
胸が熱くなるよ
My heart starts racing
腹筋だって割れてるし…
Even your abs are ripped...
これを持って！
Hold this!
Hmm, you really are mysterious, aren't you?
Or maybe it's just that I like exploring stars.
Hey! Hey hey! Will you help me get past my embarrassment?
Bau bau!
髪をかきあげながら ため息つくように
While running my fingers through my hair, like letting out a sigh
反応を見るわ わるきー
I'll watch your reaction, the bad girl
筋肉を触らせてよ どれくらい硬いの？
Let me touch your muscles, how hard are they?
女の子には興味津々
Girls are very curious
逞しさ見てみたいのよ
I want to see your sturdiness
どんな感じなのかい？
What does it feel like?
ワクワクしてるわ
I'm getting excited
上腕二頭筋てセクシーだね
Biceps are sexy, aren't they?
全部持って！
Hold it all!
Oh no! Mococo's side show is ending!
Well then, can you close your eyes for me?
Hey, why are you peeking? Gosh!
Bau bau!
Oh! What did you think, Ruffians?
My performance, Mococo in a play...
Mococo-chan's Warukii!
Mococo-chan!
Why did it have to be such an embarrassing song, though?
I thought it fit you perfectly, Mococo-chan! Bau bau!
Huh? Was it okay, Ruffians?
Was it... sexy?
いえす。
Yes.
It was... It was...
えー、もしかしたらこれの練習をすればいいんじゃない、モコちゃん？
Um, maybe we could work on that, Mococo-chan?
わお！
Whoa!
もしかしたら、最初にできることは...
Maybe the first thing we can do for that...
ある先輩から特別なレッスンを受けることだよ！
...is get some special lessons from a certain senpai!
おお！おお！
Oh! Oh!
この先輩、絶対にセクシーの女王に違いないと思うんだ！
You know this senpai, I think she must absolutely be the queen of sexiness!
呼んでみよう！　おっけー！
Let's call her on! Okay!
マリン船長先輩！
Marine Senpai!
Ahoy! Ahoy!
Ahoy!
ハッピーバースデー！
Happy birthday!
ありがとうございます！　可愛い！
Thank you! So cute!
フワモコサンド！あ、フワモコサンド！気持ちいい！わお！Ahoy!
FUWAMOCO sandwich! Ah, FUWAMOCO sandwich! It feels so good! Wow! Ahoy!
それでセクシーになりたいんですって？
So you want to become sexy?
そう！さっきのあの曲どうだった、モコちゃんとセクシーしてた？
That's right! How was that song earlier? Was I being sexy with Mococo-chan?
おお？　うーん...
Oh? Hmm...
（セクシーなポーズ）
(Sexy poses)
何見てるんですか？
What are you looking at?
まあ、まあ。セクシー... 全体のスタイル...
Well, well. Sexy... overall, your style...
あ、セクシー！
Ah, sexy!
セクシー！あ！モコちゃんも...
Sexy! Ah! Mococo-chan too...
あ、お胸が...え？セクシー、セクシー。
Ah, chest... eh? Sexy, sexy.
あ！しっぽ触っちゃダメですよ、船長先輩！
Ah! You can't touch my tail, Marine-senpai!
何でダメなの？
Why not?
何で？！ダメダメダメ！
Why?! No, no, no!
ダメですよ！　ダメか。　ダメですよ！
No! It's no good! Is it no good? It's no good!
船長！モコはもっとセクシーになれますか？
Captain! Can Mococo become more sexy?
そうですね。じゃあちょっとセクシーショットを今から撮っていきましょう！
I see. Then, let's take some sexy shots now!
おっけー！
Okay!
じゃあカメラ用意しますね！
Then I'll get the camera ready!
お願いします！カメラカモン！あ、来た来た来た！早いよ！
Please do! Camera, come on! Oh, it's here! It's fast!
はい！帽子もらっちゃった！
Yes! I got a hat!
私も被ってる！
I'm wearing it too!
おいそれ船長帽だぞ！勝手に被るな！Ahoy!
Hey, that's the Captain's hat! Don't just put it on! Ahoy!
これセクシーなのかな？
I wonder if this is sexy...
これセクシーじゃないね！
This isn't sexy at all, is it?
はい、行きます！もっと下！もっと下！
Okay, here we go! Lower! Go lower!
え、ちょっと待って！ちょっと待って！
Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
もっと！モコちゃん、逃げ...あ、モコちゃん逃げてった。
More! Mococo-chan, escape... Ah, Mococo-chan ran away.
じゃあ、ほなフワワ...フワワ...
Now, Fuwawa... Fuwawa...
フワワもダメです！あ、ダメです！
Fuwawa is no good either! Ah, no good!
ダメですか？船長先輩... Ahoy!
Is it no good? Captain-senpai... Ahoy!
じゃあ、そな...じゃあ、はい。もう一回、一緒に。モコちゃんが考えるセクシーポーズって何？
Well then... okay, then. One more time, together. Mococo-chan, what's a sexy pose you can think of?
確かに！見せて！にゃあ！にゃあ！にゃあ！
I see! Let's see! Nyaa! Nyaa! Nyaa!
窓口はあると思いますけど！
I think there's a window for this!
おっけー。じゃあ最後に３、２、１でAhoy！
Okay. Finally, let's say 'Ahoy' on 3, 2, 1!
おっけー！じゃあ３、２、１...
Okay! 3, 2, 1...
Ahoy！
Ahoy!
ぷるぷるぷるぷる...
Purupurupurupuru...
モコも！ぷるぷるぷるぷる...
Mococo too! Purupurupurupuru...
頑張った！頑張った、頑張った！
You worked hard! We worked hard!
みんな覚えてる？今日はライブなんです！
Everyone, remember? Today is a concert!
そうだよ、今日はライブだよね！こんなことしてる場合じゃない！
That's right, today is a concert! This is no time for this!
歌いに来たんだよ！
We're here to sing!
そう！マリン船長先輩のあの曲を一緒に歌いましょう！
So, let's sing one of our favorite songs by Marine-senpai!
じゃあ行きましょうか！
Shall we go?
Ahoy！！ 我ら宝鐘海賊団☆
Ahoy!! We are the Houshou Pirates!
海賊なら　ヨーホー
If you're a pirate, Yo-ho!
踊るだけで　ヨーホー
Just dancing, Yo-ho!
さあみんな　旗の下へ
Come everyone, under the flag!
宝鐘海賊団
Houshou Pirates!
出航！
Set sail!
Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy!
踊るAhoyに見るAhoy
The dancing Ahoy and the watching Ahoy
全速前進だー！
Full speed ahead!
進め！
Advance!
太陽さんさん大航海日和だ
Sun is shining, a great day for voyaging
歌え！
Sing!
最高のテンション波の音に乗せどんぶらこ
Highest tension, riding the sound of the waves, rocking along
海でガールズパーティー
Girls' party at sea
おかえり兄貴がハッピー
Welcome back, brother is happy
面舵ドッパドッパひらひら
Starboard, splash splash, fluttering
山奥ボロボロマイハウスで夢を見て
Dreaming in my run-down house deep in the mountains
あ、神様！いつかこのフワモコを本物の海賊にしてください！
Ah, God! Please make FUWAMOCO real pirates one day!
声を上げてさあ出航だ我ら宝鐘海賊団
Raise your voice, let's set sail, we are the Houshou Pirates
コンパス片手に旗を掲げこの海をジャックしちゃおう
Compass in one hand, raising the flag, let's jack this sea
よそ見ついておいで共にヨーホー叫ぼう
Don't look away, follow us, let's shout Yo-ho together
ああ最高の日々へようこそ我が...
Ah, to the best days, welcome to our...
...船へ
...to the ship
アホイ！ アホイ！ アホイ！ アホイ！
Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy!
踊るアホイ 見るアホイ (ホイホイ！)
Dancing Ahoy, Watching Ahoy (Hoi hoi!)
アホイ！ アホイ！ アホイ！ (ホイホイホイ！)
Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy! (Hoi hoi hoi!)
1、2、サンバ！ サンバ！
1, 2, samba! samba!
熱く (熱く！) 煽るパッション
Hotly (Hotly!) Fan the passion
想いを解き放て
Set your feelings free
赤く (赤く！) 煌めくパッション
Redly (Redly!) Sparkling passion
形から入るタイプで
I'm the type who starts with the appearance
発射 10秒前
Launch! 10 seconds before
走れ ガチ恋で (フフ！)
Run with true love (Fufu!)
焼きもち焼けるわ
I'm getting jealous
ギラギラ
Sparkling
じんわり汗も滴るいい女
A fine woman dripping with a bit of sweat
だけど
But...
あぁ 神様... 船長はセンシティブだとBANされちゃうのですね はにゃ〜〜ん
Ah, God... If the Captain is too sensitive, she'll get banned, won't she? Hanyann~
奪われたら取り戻せ
If it's stolen, take it back!
それが宝鐘海賊団
That's the Houshou Pirates
君たちとなら辿り着ける
With you all, we can reach
伝説のエ・ル・ド・ラ・ド (ゴーゴー！)
The legendary El Dorado (Go go!)
夜空 楽しけりゃ 歌えヨーホー
The night sky, if it's fun, sing Yo-ho!
ヨーホー パーリナイッ！
Yo-ho! Party night!
あぁ この景色
Ah, this scenery
大切な仲間よ
My precious comrades
宴だ宴だ 騒げや騒げ
It's a banquet! It's a banquet! Make some noise! Make some noise!
踊るアホイ 見るアホイ (ホイホイ！)
Dancing Ahoy, Watching Ahoy (Hoi hoi!)
同じアホなら踊らなきゃ損損
If we're all fools, it's a loss not to dance!
酒樽片手に行きますよ それっ！
Let's go with a sake barrel in hand! There!
アホイ アホイ アホイ アホイ
Ahoy Ahoy Ahoy Ahoy
宝鐘マリン (宝鐘マリン)
Houshou Marine (Houshou Marine)
世界で一番 (可愛いよ！)
In all the world (You're the cutest!)
メスガキ メスガキ (メスガキ メスガキ)
Mesugaki, mesugaki (Mesugaki, mesugaki)
エロガキ エロガキ (エロガキ エロガキ)
Erogaki, erogaki (Erogaki, erogaki)
ボンッキュッボンッ (ボンッキュッボンッ)
Boom-curve-boom (Boom-curve-boom)
熟女 パツパツの (シマシマショーツ！)
Mature woman, tight (Striped shorts!)
お宝 お宝 (お宝 お宝)
Treasure treasure (Treasure treasure)
マザイ マザイ (マザイ マザイ)
Mazai mazai (Mazai mazai)
投げ銭ドカン (投げ銭ドカン)
Donations boom (Donations boom)
船長のちょっといいとこ (見てみたい！)
The Captain's good points (I want to see them!)
アハン アハン (もっと もっと)
A-han A-han (More, more)
ウフン ウフン (もっと もっと)
U-fun U-fun (More, more)
セクシービーム (もっと もっと)
Sexy beam (More, more)
やんまいちんぐ (もっと もっと)
Yanmaichingu (More, more)
だっちゅーの (もっと もっと)
Dacchu-no (More, more)
さーびすさーびす (もっと もっと)
Service, service (More, more)
萌え萌えキュン (もっと もっと)
Moe moe kyun (More, more)
出会って5秒で (即出航〜〜！！！)
5 seconds after meeting (Immediate departure!!!)
あぁ もう 船長は君たちをそんな子に育てた覚えはありません 本当に... メッ！ だぞっ
Ah, jeez. The Captain doesn't remember raising you to be such kids. Really... Bad! I say.
立てば痴女 座れば娼婦 歩く姿は センシティブ
Standing, she's a lewd woman; sitting, she's a harlot; walking, she's sensitive.
夢を見ようよ この船で 後悔なんてさせない
Let's dream on this ship, I won't let you regret it.
君たちのおかげで私は 船長になれるから
Because of you all, I can be the Captain.
いけいけ！ 船長キャノン！ 打てぇ〜〜〜！
Go go! Captain Cannon! Fire~~~!
どっか〜〜ん！
Boom~~!
声を上げて さぁ出航だ
Raise your voices, come now, it's time to set sail!
我ら宝鐘海賊団
We are the Houshou Pirates.
コンパス片手に 旗を上げ
With a compass in one hand, raise the flag,
この海をジャックしちゃおう
let's jack this sea!
夜空 ついておいで ともにヨーホー
The night sky, follow me, together Yo-ho!
ヨーホー 叫べよ
Yo-ho! Shout it out!
最高の秘密
The greatest secret,
ようこそ我が船へ
welcome to my ship.
宝鐘の海賊団 (Ahoy!)
Houshou Pirates (Ahoy!)
それでは行きますよ 出航〜〜！！
Well then, here we go! Departure~~!!
ヨーソロ〜〜！⚓️
Yousoro~~!⚓️
Welcome to ようこそジャパリパーク！
Welcome to, welcome to Japari Park!
今日もドッタンバッタン大騒ぎ
Today's another rackety, clattery big fuss.
ようこそジャパリパークへ イヌ科のみんな ワンワン！
Welcome to Japari Park! To all the canines, wan wan!
うー！ がぉー！
Uhh! Gaoo!
高らかに笑い笑えば
If we laugh out loud,
フレンズ フレンズ
friends, friends.
喧嘩して すったもんだしても
Even if we fight and have all sorts of trouble,
仲良し
we're good friends.
けものはいても のけものはいない
There are beasts, but no outcasts,
本当の愛はここにある
true love is right here.
ほら 君も
Look, you too,
手をつないで大冒険
hold hands for a big adventure!
(ワン、ツー、スリー)
(One, two, three)
Welcome to ようこそジャパリパーク！
Welcome to, welcome to Japari Park!
今日もドッタンバッタン大騒ぎ
Today's another rackety, clattery big fuss.
姿かたちも十人十色
Shapes and sizes, to each their own,
だから惹かれ合うの
that's why we're drawn to each other.
夕暮れ空に
When we gently lay our fingers together
指をそっと重ねたら
against the twilight sky.
はじめまして (はじめまして)
Nice to meet you (Nice to meet you),
君をもっと知りたいな
I want to know more about you.
うー！ がぉー！
Uhh! Gaoo!
振り向けば あちらこちらで
If you look back, there's trouble,
トラブル トラブル
trouble here and there.
なんてこった てんやわんや
What a mess, all helter-skelter,
珍紛漢紛 止まんない
gibberish, it won't stop!
うー！
Uhh!
...も ほどほどに見ててね
...and look at us properly.
みんな自由に生きている
Everyone is living freely.
そう 日々も 飾らなくて大丈夫
Yes, our daily lives don't need to be fancy.
（はい どうぞ）
(Go ahead!)
Nice to meet you ジャパリパーク！
Nice to meet you, Japari Park!
今日からはどうぞよろしくね
Let's get along from today onwards.
いつもいつでも優しい笑顔
With a kind smile always and forever,
君を待っていたの
I've been waiting for you.
開かれた扉 夢をいっぱい語ったら
Through the open door, if we talk about many dreams,
どこまででも
To wherever it leads,
続いてく
It will continue,
グレイトジャーニー
This Great Journey.
東へ吠えろ
Howl to the east!
西へ吠えろ
Howl to the west!
世界中に響けサファリメロディ
Let the safari melody echo throughout the world!
Welcome to ようこそジャパリパーク！
Welcome to Japari Park!
今日もドッタンバッタン大騒ぎ
Today is another hectic ruckus.
姿かたちも十人十色 だから惹かれ合うの
Shapes and sizes are all different, so we're drawn together.
夕暮れ空に指をそっと重ねたら
If we gently overlap our fingers in the sunset sky,
はじめまして
Nice to meet you.
君をもっと知りたいな
I want to know more about you.
うーがう！
U-Gau!
ララララ ララララ
La la la la, la la la la
Oh, Welcome to the ジャパリパーク！
Oh, Welcome to the Japari Park!
ララララ ララララ
La la la la, la la la la
集まれ友達
Gather 'round, friends!
ララララ ララララ
La la la la, la la la la
Oh, Welcome to the ジャパリパーク！
Oh, Welcome to the Japari Park!
ララララ ララララ
La la la la, la la la la
素敵な旅立ち
A wonderful departure!
ようこそジャパリパーク！
Welcome to Japari Park!
あらゆる困難が科学で解決するこの平成の時代
In this Heisei era, where all difficulties are solved by science...
人々の閉ざされた心の闇に蔓延る
Infesting the darkness of people's closed hearts...
魑魅魍魎が存在していた
Evil spirits and monsters existed.
科学の力ではどうしようも出来ないその奇怪な輩に立ち向かう
Confronting those strange folks that cannot be helped by science,
神妙不可思議にて 胡散臭い男がひとり
A man, mysterious and shady, is there alone.
その名は 矢部野彦麿（やべのひこまろ）
His name is Hikomaro Yabeno.
そう 人は彼を陰陽師と呼ぶ
Yes, people call him an Onmyoji.
＊自称
*Self-proclaimed
悪霊退散！ 悪霊退散！
Evil spirits, begone! Evil spirits, begone!
怨霊 ものの怪 困った時は
Vengeful ghosts, monsters, when you're in trouble...
ドーマン！セーマン！ ドーマン！セーマン！
Doman! Seman! Doman! Seman!
直ぐに呼びましょ陰陽師 レッツゴー！
Let's call an Onmyoji right away, let's go!
死してなお この世に未練 残せしは 魑魅魍魎と
Those who leave regrets in this world even after death...
成り果てる その悪しき血を清めるが 陰陽の道
...will turn into monsters. To purify their evil blood is the way of Onmyo.
人の世に 生まれし悪を
The evil born into the human world...
闇へと
...into the darkness...
葬れよ
...bury it!
悪霊退散！ 悪霊退散！
Evil spirits, begone! Evil spirits, begone!
妖怪 あやかし 困った時は
Yōkai, apparitions, when you're in trouble...
ドーマン！セーマン！ ドーマン！セーマン！
Doman! Seman! Doman! Seman!
助けてもらおう陰陽師 レッツゴー！
Let's get help from an Onmyoji, let's go!
生きながら 怨み憎しみ 募りしは 悪鬼悪霊
Vengeance and hatred accumulated while living turn into evil demons.
呼び覚ます その激昂を宥めるも 陰陽の道
To soothe the fury they awaken is the way of Onmyo.
愛しさの 行き着く果てに
At the end of where love reaches...
病む心
...the suffering heart...
慰めよ
...comfort it!
悪霊退散！ 悪霊退散！
Evil spirits, begone! Evil spirits, begone!
怨念 怨恨 困った時は
Grudges, resentment, when you're in trouble...
ドーマン！セーマン！ ドーマン！セーマン！
Doman! Seman! Doman! Seman!
鎮めてもらおう陰陽師 レッツゴー！
Let's have the Onmyoji calm them down, let's go!
うううううううううう...
Uuuuuuuuuu...
辛い時、悲しい時...
In times of pain, in times of sadness...
人はそんな時、心の隙間に闇が出来る。
In moments like those, darkness forms in the gaps of the heart.
その心の闇に、魔物たちは容赦なく入り込んでくるのだ！
Into that darkness, monsters will crawl in without mercy!
だから、苦しくても、くじけるな！
So even if it's painful, do not falter!
落ち込むな！くよくよするな！
Do not be depressed! Do not dwell on it!
何事にも屈しない...
A resilient heart that never gives in to anything...
強靭な心こそが最強の武器なのだから！
...is the ultimate weapon of all!
寂しさで ゆらめく心を
Loneliness preys on a wavering heart...
心を 狙うもの
...a heart being targeted.
打ち砕け！
Smash it to pieces!
悪霊退散！悪霊退散！
Evil spirits, begone! Evil spirits, begone!
超常現象 困った時は
When you're troubled by paranormal phenomena...
ドーマン！セーマン！ドーマン！セーマン！
Doman! Seman! Doman! Seman!
祓ってもらおう 陰陽師 レッツゴー！
Let the Onmyoji exorcise them! Let's go!
悪霊退散！悪霊退散！
Evil spirits, begone! Evil spirits, begone!
呪い呪われ 困った時は
When you're troubled by curses and hexes...
ドーマン！セーマン！ドーマン！セーマン！
Doman! Seman! Doman! Seman!
相談しましょう 陰陽師 レッツゴー！
Let's consult the Onmyoji! Let's go!
やっぱり頼れる 陰陽師 レッツゴー！
You can always count on the Onmyoji! Let's go!
みんなのヒーロー 陰！陽！師！
Everyone's hero! On! Myo! Ji!
成仏しろよ！
Pass on peacefully!
BAU BAU! Hi!
Do you wanna party together with us? ...Bau Bau!
You know we had some of our Holo-Dog Senpai join us for Yocoso Jappari-party...
...and then performed an extra silly version of Let's Go! Onmyoji!
What was that with the bells and the microwave?!
You know, that's the necessary part of Let's Go! Onmyoji, you know!
I guess... extra silly!
We're just so happy to have a bunch of our friends here with us for our birthday live today.
It's been really special so far, huh?
But! But! We're still not done!
Fuwamoco-time is still going! You're not tired yet, Ruffians?
No? Not time, right?!
Yeah! Wow, Ruffians!
You know, it's our special day today...
...but actually, we have something we'd like to surprise you with!
Are you ready? Can we get a drum roll?
Tadaa! Our birthday merchandise!
Here we have a Fuwawa birthday set and a Mococo birthday set! Bau Bau!
Well... this year's birthday merch is a little bit embarrassing.
I sure it's gonna be okay, Fuwawa. It's gonna be okay.
I'm sure it's gonna be okay, Fuwawa. It's gonna be okay.
I know a lot of Ruffians have been waiting for a long time for something like this, but...
Press that! Tada! We have the definitive FUWAMOCO dakimakura cover!
Finally, right?! You know, Ruffians! You know, right?!
You can't just have Fuwa on one side and me on the other, okay? That's not okay! Got it?!
So that's why we have a Fuwawa version and a Mococo version!
Of course, with beautiful illustrations... but I love them!
イコモチ！イコモチ！ありがとう！Thank you!
Ikomochi! Ikomochi! Arigato! Thank you!
Wow! This is the Fuwawa dakimakura.
And here is the Mococo dakimakura. Bau bau!
They're very big. Mococo-chan, Mococo-chan...
Fuwawa-chan! Bau bau!
They're for hugging.
They're for hugging. Yes.
But you know, even though they might be a little bit embarrassing...
We hope that they can help you sleep soundly at night, you know?
Bau bau! Bau bau!
And next, we have Fuwamoco keychain plushies!
Look how compact they are! Compact!
But now, Fuwamoco can go anywhere and everywhere along with you.
Attached to your bag, maybe your keys, maybe even in your car.
No matter what, we'll be by your side. It's super cute!
And next, we have a very cute Fuwawa hairband and Mococo hairband.
Maybe you're wondering, what exactly is this?
Well, this way we can help keep back the fluff from your face when you wash your face at night.
Or maybe you can just have fun with a quick Fuwamoco style disguise!
It's up to you!
And finally, we have some cute collectible button badges of dakimakura Fuwamoco.
They're sparkly and holographic, and come in a super cute heart shape.
It's perfect for any ita-bag, you know? Just bringing a bit more Fuwamoco to your belongings.
But we also have something special as well, right Mococo-chan?
You know, what would help you get an even better rest at night, right?
Maybe a soothing sleepover ASMR voice from us? There's a Fuwawa voice...
...and a Mococo voice. But we hope that you'll listen to both of them right before bed.
And finally, for those who purchase the entire set, we also have a special thank you bonus voice message as well.
And of course, there are also special hand-signed limited edition sets that come with a polaroid style card.
So cute! We really hope that you'll be able to get your paws on them as well, Ruffians!
And as a full set bonus, you'll receive one card that can be used in the Hololive Official Card Game!
Yeah, one card for Fuwawa's set, one card for Mococo's set. And this card is only available to those who purchase from the Hololive Production Official Shop.
Okay, got it! Please look forward to it, okay? Bau bau!
You know, after that very exciting announcement...
...we still have one last song we'd like to sing for you today.
Well, this next song is one that's really important to us, especially when we were still locked up back in the cell.
And now that we're finally a part of Hololive, and you know, we're even able to have our first ever birthday live...
...we'd like to sing it for you. Okay? Please listen, Kirameki Rider!
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our newborn hearts resonate
最高な時間　最高の仲間と
The best time with the best friends
キラメキに乗って☆
Riding on the sparkle☆
Yeah! Bau bau!
覚えてるかな？　最初の歌
Do you remember? Our first song
懐かしいね
How nostalgic
渡し声が震えていた
My voice was trembling
あの日から続く未来は
The future that continues from that day
みんなと掴んだ今日だよ
Is today, which we grabbed with everyone
もっともっともっともっと
More, more, more, more
加速するハート
My heart is accelerating
一緒に行くよ　どこまでも
We'll go together, anywhere
I'm ready! 準備はオッケー！
I'm ready! Ready to go!
開け夢の扉を
Open the door to your dreams
1 2 3 キラメキライダー
1 2 3 Kirameki Rider
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let the fresh heart-throbs resound
最高の時間　最高の仲間と
The best time, with the best friends
ここにいるよ　見つけてくれたから
I'm right here, because you found me
君に会いたくてやって来たんだ　みんなで歌おう
I came here because I wanted to see you, let's all sing together
終わらないメロディ
Never-ending melody
キラメキに乗って
Ride on the sparkle
イェーイ！
Yeah!
バウ！バウ！バウ！バウ！
Bau! Bau! Bau! Bau!
届いてるかな？　私の声　Ah 君と
Is it reaching you? My voice, ah, with you
届けたいのは　君に笑顔　For Your Smile
What I want to deliver is a smile for you, for your smile
理想の高さに　悔しくて
Frustrated by the height of ideals
見送る背中　泣き笑ったね
Watching your back as you left, we laughed and cried
ギュッとギュッとギュッとギュッと　すべて抱きしめて
Tightly, tightly, tightly, tightly, embracing everything
一緒に行こう　どこまでも
Let's go together, no matter how far
I'm ready! 準備はオッケー！
I'm ready! Ready to go!
進め希望の道を
Move forward on the path of hope
1 2 3 キラメキライダー
1 2 3 Kirameki Rider
好きな気持ち　カラフルに奏でたいな
I want to play my feelings of love colorfully
最高の場所　最高のみんなと
The best place, with everyone who's the best
ここにいるよ　幻なんかじゃない
I'm right here, it's not an illusion
君の心が幸せに染まるように
So that your heart may be dyed in happiness
重ねていくハーモニー
Layering the harmony
キラメキ纏って
Wrapped in sparkle
歌い続けたいな
I want to keep singing
踊り続けたいな
I want to keep dancing
そんな願い　わがままでもいいでしょう
A wish like that, it's okay even if it's selfish, right?
だって楽しすぎて　もう止まらない
Because it's just too much fun, I can't stop anymore
輝くステージで　もっともっと
On the shining stage, more and more
(お願い)　ずっと
(Please) forever
イェーイ！
Yeah!
バウバウ！
Bau bau!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
嬉しい　楽しい　愛しいだけじゃ語れない
Happy, fun, dear... it can't be told by those alone
今も今も悩みはあるけれど
Even now, even now, there are worries, but
ここにいるよ　私ここにいるよ
I'm right here, I'm right here
君と同じ世界を見つめて
Gazing at the same world as you
いくよ！ キラメキライダー
Here we go! Kirameki Rider
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let the fresh heart-throbs resound
最高の時間　最高の仲間と
The best time, with the best friends
ここにいるよ　見つけてくれたから
I'm right here, because you found me
君に会いたくてやって来たんだ　みんなで歌おう
I came here because I wanted to see you, let's all sing together
せーの！
One, two!
終わらないメロディ
Never-ending melody
キラメキに乗って☆
Ride on the sparkle☆
キラメキ纏って
Wrapped in sparkle
イェーイ！
Yeah!
バウバウ！
Bau bau!
アンコール！
Encore!
愛・おぼえていますか
Do You Remember Love?
Lyrics: 安井かずみ Music: 加藤和彦
Lyrics: Yasui Kazumi Music: Kato Kazuhiko
今 あなたの声が聴こえる
Now I can hear your voice
「ここにおいで」と
Saying, "Come over here"
淋しさに 負けそうな わたしに
To me, who was about to give in to loneliness
今 あなたの姿が見える
Now I can see your figure
歩いてくる
Walking towards me
目を閉じて 待っている わたしに
To me, who is waiting with eyes closed
昨日まで 涙でくもってた
Until yesterday, it was clouded with tears
心は今...
But my heart now...
おぼえていますか
Do you remember?
目と目が合った時を
The moment when our eyes met?
おぼえていますか
Do you remember?
手と手が触れあった時
The moment when our hands touched?
それは初めての
That was the first
愛の旅立ちでした
Journey of love
I love you, so
今 あなたの視線感じる
Now I feel your gaze
離れてても
Even if we are apart
体中が 暖かくなるの
My whole body becomes warm
今 あなたの愛信じます
Now I believe in your love
どうぞわたしを 遠くから見守って下さい
Please watch over me from afar
昨日まで 涙でくもってた
Until yesterday, it was clouded with tears
世界は今...
The world now...
おぼえていますか
Do you remember?
目と目が合った時を
The moment when our eyes met?
おぼえていますか
Do you remember?
手と手が触れあった時
The moment when our hands touched?
それは初めての
That was the first
愛の旅立ちでした
Journey of love
I love you, so
もう ひとりぼっちじゃない
I'm not all alone anymore
あなたがいるから
Because you are here
おぼえていますか
Do you remember?
目と目が合った時を
The moment when our eyes met?
おぼえていますか
Do you remember?
手と手が触れあった時
The moment when our hands touched?
それは初めての
That was the first
愛の旅立ちでした
Journey of love
I love you, so
もう ひとりぼっちじゃない
I'm not all alone anymore
あなたがいるから
Because you are here
もう ひとりぼっちじゃない
I'm not all alone anymore
あなたがいるから
Because you are here
もう ひとりぼっちじゃない
I'm not all alone anymore
あなたがいるから
Because you are here
Bau bau!
Thank you so much for the encore! Thank you!
It was really special. Yeah.
We kept you waiting, huh?
Yeah, sorry about that.
But it means a lot to us.
Really, thank you!
Thank you!
Bau bau! Bau bau!
Wow, this has been an unforgettable first birthday, huh?
Yeah! That we'll treasure forever and ever!
And you know, us, Fuwa...
I'm a little bit hungry, you know?
Mococo!
Don't you feel a little hungry after singing
and dancing all those songs, huh?
But you know, right now, and Mococo, we could be...
Can't we just have a quick bite? Huh?
Is that okay, Ruffian?
You won't mind, right?
Just a little bite.
Okay!
Bau bau!
Yeah!
いただきます！
Let's eat!
(Eating sounds)
Ah! Bau bau!
Bau bau!
So yummy!
Mm!
Mococo, this is the best cake ever!
Wow!
My tummy's all full now,
so let's do our best, you know?
I guess we do have some important stuff to talk about, huh?
Yeah.
Okay! Let's go!
Woah!
Ah, wait, Mococo!
I think there's some cream on your face.
Right over here. Mm!
Hey! You ate it, huh?!
You know!
It was yummy.
Mococo, you still have cream on your face!
Still!
Ah, maybe just one more... let's just get it all!
Okay!
Ah, well, where was I?
Ah, our birthday, huh?
Yeah!
We're super happy to be able to share and perform
some of my favorite songs with you today.
As well as show lots of different sides of ourselves as idols.
We've put all into our performance today, you know?
Our fluff and our fights.
Sweat and tears, but most importantly,
so much of our love.
So we hope they're able to shine just even a little bit.
Well, we'll continue to do our best,
so please continue to cheer lots for us, okay?
We'll do our best to go into even stronger demon-guard dogs, yeah!
To protect your smile, okay?
Don't take your eyes off us!
Mm! You know!
Fuwamoco, we'll continue to keep an eye on you too, okay?
Yeah.
Bau bau!
Yeah!
Well, with that, we'd like to go into our
final final song for today. Final final.
But before, for the Ruffians who are all part
of our membership, the Doggy Pack...
Have you joined? Uh...
Yeah!
Well, we still have a few more songs we'd like to sing
from our hearts to yours. Yeah.
You know, just a little heart to heart.
So we hope... don't, don't run off,
don't go anywhere after this, okay? Don't, don't go away, okay?
Mm, there's just a little more we'd like to share with you. Yeah.
Got it. Uh...
Well, please wait a little while while we wipe off some of our sweat
and fix ourselves up and fuzz a little, okay?
But you know, in the meantime, maybe you can get your paws
on some of our birthday merch as well! Birthday merch! Yeah.
But really, thank you so much for being a Ruffian.
Yeah. We'll continue to do our all.
So let's continue on this bright journey together, okay?
Uh... woah!
Well, this last song is especially dear to us,
and has kept us going when times have been tough too. Uh...
We know and hope that you'll know we'll always be here for you,
and that someone out there will be always waiting.
So do your best, okay?
Well then, please listen to our last song.
ゆめのばとん。
Yume no Baton.
ゆめのばとん
Lyrics, Music 井上ほるこ
Yume no Baton
Lyrics, Music by Inoue Horuko
きっとこの世界のどこかに
Surely, somewhere in this world,
君だけの果ての世界...
...there's a world only for you...
きっとこの世界のどこかに
Surely somewhere in this world,
君だけをずっと待ってる人がいるから
there is someone who has been waiting only for you.
コートのポケットから
From a coat pocket,
くしゃくしゃの紙切れ
a crumpled piece of paper,
映画の半券
a movie stub,
あの日の情景
the scene of that day.
一緒に見に行ったね
We went to see it together,
帰り道気づいたら
and on the way back we realized
電車もなくなるくらい
that the trains had even stopped running
語り合った
as we talked and talked.
思い出しして あの情熱
Recalling it, that passion.
溢れてくるメロディ
The melody that overflows,
振り返ったら
when I look back,
君が笑顔で
you're there smiling
手を振る
and waving.
きっとこの世界のどこかに
Surely somewhere in this world,
君だけを
only you...
ずっと待ってる
who has been waiting all along,
人がいる
there is someone.
誰にも振り回されないで
Don't let anyone push you around,
君だけの
your very own...
好きやときめきに
to your likes and excitements,
素直でいて
stay true.
そっと差し出した
Gently held out,
夢のバトン
the baton of dreams,
確かに受け取ったよ
I certainly received it,
あの時
back then.
駅前のベンチに座って
Sitting on a bench in front of the station,
缶ジュース片手に
with a can of juice in one hand,
未来を
the future...
眺めてた
we were gazing at.
広場にはビルが立って
A building stands in the plaza now,
あの店もないけど
and that shop is gone too,
レンガの壁や足跡は
but the brick walls and footprints
そのままだね
remain just the same.
ここに来れば
If I come here,
君に会えるよ
I can meet you.
そんな気がするんだ
That's the feeling I get.
鳴り出した
Started to ring,
シグナルが
the signal...
青に
to green...
なれば
when it turns.
きっとこの世界のどこかに
Surely somewhere in this world,
楽しげな
joyful...
声に沈む
sinking into voices,
人がいる
there is someone.
待っててね
Wait for me,
今すぐ会いに行くよ
I'm coming to see you right now.
寂しさを包み込んで
I'll wrap up the loneliness
優しさに変えて
and turn it into kindness.
君からもらった
I received it from you,
夢のバトン
the baton of dreams,
静かに
quietly,
輝き出す
it begins to shine.
きっとこの世界のどこかに
Surely somewhere in this world,
君だけをずっと待ってる
there is someone who has been
人がいるから
waiting only for you.
誰にも振り回されないで
Don't let anyone push you around,
君だけの
your very own...
好きやときめきに
to your likes and excitements,
素直でいて
stay true.
そっと差し出した
Gently held out,
夢のバトン
the baton of dreams,
確かに受け取ったよ
I certainly received it.
季節がいくつ
No matter how many seasons
巡っても
pass by,
どんなに遠く
no matter how far
離れても
apart we are.
忘れないよ
I won't forget,
君のこと
about you.
夢見ていれば
If we keep dreaming,
また会える
we can meet again.
ありがとう
Thank you.
SEE YOU AT OUR ENCORE LIVE IN MEMBERSHIP!
メン限アンコールライブ待っててねー！
Wait for the members-only encore live!
FUWAMOCO Birthday Party Night
SEE YOU AT OUR ENCORE LIVE IN MEMBERSHIP!
メン限アンコールライブで待ってるよー！
Waiting for you at the members-only encore live!